<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Colorado Reed</title>
    <link>https://1337potato.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Colorado Reed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://1337potato.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reacting is Easier</title>
      <link>https://1337potato.com/posts/reactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1337potato.com/posts/reactions/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s easier to let other people find things to do with my time. React to their needs.
It feels productive to make progress for others. To see that I can help them.
Responding to emails, attending meetings, looking at Slack alerts.
So I sit down to do some deep work: some heavy thought about big projects. And I find myself checking my email and looking for Slack alerts. Secretly hoping someone else will block out the next hour for me, so that I don&amp;rsquo;t have to drive forward my own thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rain on Leaves</title>
      <link>https://1337potato.com/posts/rain-on-leaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1337potato.com/posts/rain-on-leaves/</guid>
      <description>Rain began to beat down on me yesterday morning.
I was trail running.
I woke up before the sun.
My mind was clear.
I was doing my part.
But the rain beat down on my path. It began to pour, and I could hear the orchestra of the raining forest: rain on leaves.
And when I think about the sound of rain on leaves, I think of relaxation. I imagine most people do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tao of Running - Everything Balances</title>
      <link>https://1337potato.com/posts/running-tao-te-ching-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1337potato.com/posts/running-tao-te-ching-2/</guid>
      <description>While reading the Tao Te Ching, I found that certain chapters connect very well with running. In order to further connect with these chapters myself, I &amp;ldquo;translated&amp;rdquo; them into a form that directly connects with running, which is a fundamental part of my life.
This is from Chapter 2 of the Tao Te Ching; translated by Stephen Mitchell:
 Seeing some runs as beautiful
makes other runs ugly
Seeing some runs as good</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
